RESUME For the post of Showroom Manager

Kamal Sharma C-14, Flat no. 201 Rail Vihar VIP Road Zirakpur Punjab- 140603 Mob.No 9501992530 E-mail:- kamalsharma46@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To associate with a progressive professionally managed organization and contribute for a mutual beneficial relationship.

PERSONAL SKILLS AND ABILITIES

Planning and controlling sales resources to maximum effect.

Possess excellent presentation, verbal & written communication skills.

Effective Planning and Organizational skills to successfully manage multiple priorities and assignments.

An experienced team player, bringing enthusiasm and energy into group efforts.

Hard working and persevering enough to meet targets and deadlines.

Education

Graduation from Punjab University, Chandigarh

Computer Literacy

Windows, MS Dos, Microsoft Word/Microsoft Excel/Power Point.

Various Internet Tools & Search Engines.

Work Experience

2017 to June 2022

Worked with Height PVC Co. Hisar Importer and Manufacturer PVC Panels as a sales manager with brand name of Height PVC Area North East.

2015 to 2016

Worked with S.V. Impex Zirakpur Importer of Pvc wall Panels as a sales manager with brand name of Decent Pvc Panels Area PB. H.P.

2012 to 2014

Worked with G.D.Internationa Ludhiana Importer of PVC wall Panles as a sales manager Area Punjab U.P H.P with brand name of wall tec.

2007 to 2011

Worked with Suruchi Spices Ltd. Nagpur as a ASM with brand name of Suruchi spices area all Punjab

2000 to 2006

Worked with Hindustan Lever Ltd. as a TSI (Main Line) area Ganganagar to Jaipur with brand name of Lux, Hamam, and Rexona.

Other Details

Father's name Late Sh. Jugal Kishore

Marital status Married

Date of Birth 10-jan-1978

Nationality Indian

Language Known English, Hindi, Punjabi

Kamal Sharma